Records of the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia; Law, Appellate, and Criminal Records; Case Papers 1802-1863
Center for Digital Research in the Humanities University of Nebraska–Lincoln
- December, Civil Appearances, 2-178, 1829 (Box 426)
- December, Civil Appearances, 180-495, 1829 (Box 427)
- December, Civil Trials, 1-163, 1829 (Box 428)
- December, Civil Trials, 165-266, 1829 (Box 429)
- December, Civil Trials, 268-358, 1829 (Box 430)
- December, Civil Trials, Appeals, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1829 (Box 431)
- December, Imparlances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1829 (Box 432)
- December, Judicials, 1-117, 1829 (Box 433)
- December, Judicials, 118-372, 1829 (Box 434)
- May, Civil Appearances, 5-179, 1830 (Box 435)
- May, Civil Appearances, 188-449, 1830 (Box 436)
- May, Civil Trials, 2-17, 1830 (Box 437)
- May, Civil Trials, 181-282, 1830 (Box 438)
- May, Civil Trials, 284-324, Criminal Appearances, 1830 (Box 439)
- May, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1830 (Box 440)
- May, Judicials, 1-214, 1830 (Box 441)
- May, Judicials, 216-321, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1830 (Box 442)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-196, 1830 (Box 443)
- December, Civil Appearances, 198-566, 1830 (Box 444)
- December, Civil Appearances, 569-612, Civil Trials, 2-138, 1830 (Box 445)
- December, Civil Trials, 141-259, 1830 (Box 446)
- December, Civil Trials, 260-331, Criminal Appearances, 1-36, 1830 (Box 447)
- December, Criminal Appearances, 37-190, Criminal Trials, 1830 (Box 448)
- December, Appeals, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1830 (Box 449)
- December, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-181, 1830 (Box 450)
- December, Judicials, 182-385, 1830 (Box 451)
- May, Civil Appearances, 1-188, 1831 (Box 452)
- May, Civil Appearances, 197-378, 1831 (Box 453)
- May, Civil Trials, 2-147, 1831 (Box 454)
- May, Civil Trials, 149-205, 1831 (Box 455)
- May, Civil Trials, 209-328, 1831 (Box 456)
- May, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1831 (Box 457)
- May, Imparlances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1831 (Box 458)
- May, Judicials, 1-171, 1831 (Box 459)
- May, Judicials, 173-285, 1831 (Box 460)
- December, Civil Appearances, 1-191, 1831 (Box 461)
- December, Civil Appearances, 198-574, 1831 (Box 462)
- December, Civil Trials, 2-151, 1831 (Box 463)
- December, Civil Trials, 156-315, 1831 (Box 464)
- December, Civil Trials, 318-397, Criminal Appearances, 1831 (Box 465)
- December, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1831 (Box 466)
- December, Imparlances, 1831 (Box 467)
- May, Civil Appearances, 5-338, 1832 (Box 468)
- May, Civil Appearances, 341-541, Civil Trials, 12-102, 1832 (Box 469)
- May, Civil Trial, 106-252, 1832 (Box 470)
- May, Civil Trials, 255-375, 1832 (Box 471)
- May, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1832 (Box 472)
- May, Imparlances, 1832 (Box 473)
- May, Judicials, 1832 (Box 474)
- November, Civil Appearances, 7-391, 1832 (Box 475)
- November, Civil Appearances, 399-686, Civil Trials, 5-147, 1832 (Box 476)
- November, Civil Trials, 150-152, 1832 (Box 477)
- November, Civil Trials, 262-408, 1832 (Box 478)
- November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1832 (Box 479)
- November, Imparlances, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1832 (Box 480)
- November, Judicials, 1-180, 1832 (Box 481)
- November, Judicials, 183-240, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1832 (Box 482)
- March, Civil Appearances, 2-240, 1833 (Box 483)
- March, Civil Appearances, 251-545, 1833 (Box 484)
- March, Civil Trials, 9-213, 1833 (Box 485)
- March, Civil Trials, 215-332, 1833 (Box 486)
- March, Civil Trials, 334-440, 1833 (Box 487)
- March, Civil Trials, 442-526, 1833 (Box 488)
- March, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1833 (Box 489)
- March, Imparlances, 1833 (Box 490)
- March, Judicials, 1833 (Box 491)
- March, Appeals, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1833 (Box 492)
- September, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, 1833 (Box 493)
- November, Civil Appearances, 5-234, 1833 (Box 494)
- November, Civil Appearances, 238-602, 1833 (Box 495)
- November, Civil Appearances, 604-836, 1833 (Box 496)
- November, Civil Trials, 9-171, 1833 (Box 497)
- November, Civil Trials, 173-258, 1833 (Box 498)
- November, Civil Trials, 260-369, 1833 (Box 499)
- November, Civil Trials, 371-472, 1833 (Box 500)
- November, Civil Trials, 474-566, 1833 (Box 501)
- November, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, 1833 (Box 502)
- November, Appeals, Imparlances, 1833 (Box 503)
- November, Judicials, 5-202, 1833 (Box 504)
- November, Judicials, 206-301, Titlings for Executions & Writs, 1833 (Box 505)
- March, Civil Appearances, 4-174, 1834 (Box 506)
- March, Civil Appearances, 176-364, 1834 (Box 507)
- March, Civil Appearances, 370-649, 1834 (Box 508)
- March, Civil Trials, 5-147, 1834 (Box 509)
- March, Civil Trials, 151-190, 1834 (Box 510)
- March, Civil Trials, 192-310, 1834 (Box 511)
- March, Civil Trials, 312-405, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1834 (Box 512)
- March, Criminal Appearances, 1834 (Box 513)
- March, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Imparlances, 1834 (Box 514)
- March, Judicials, 1834 (Box 515)
- November, Civil Appearances, 3-336, 1834 (Box 516)
- November, Civil Appearances, 340-713, 1834 (Box 517)
- November, Civil Appearances, 723-1032, 1834 (Box 518)
- November, Civil Trials, 1-203, 1834 (Box 519)
- November, Civil Trials, 206-345, 1834 (Box 520)
- November, Civil Trials, 350-466, 1834 (Box 521)
- November, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1834 (Box 522)
- November, Appeals, Imparlances, 1834 (Box 523)
- November, Judicials, 3-135, 1834 (Box 524)
- November, Judicials, 155-277, 1834 (Box 525)
- November, Judicials, 279-302, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1834 (Box 526)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1-138, 1835 (Box 527)
- March, Civil Appearances, 140-320, 1835 (Box 528)
- March, Civil Appearances, 325-513, Civil Trials, 2-118, 1835 (Box 529)
- March, Civil Trials, 121-250, 1835 (Box 530)
- March, Civil Trials, 253-354, 1835 (Box 531)
- March, Civil Trials, 357-471, 1835 (Box 532)
- March, Criminal Appearances, 16-138, 1835 (Box 533)
- March, Criminal Appearances, 143-176, Criminal Trials, Appeals, Imparlances, 5-298, 1835 (Box 534)
- March, Imparlances, 308-781, Judicials, 1-69, 1835 (Box 535)
- March, Judicials, 71-210, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1835 (Box 536)
- November, Civil Appearances, 1-159, 1835 (Box 537)
- November, Civil Appearances, 161-356, 1835 (Box 538)
- November, Civil Appearances, 360-700, 1835 (Box 539)
- November, Civil Trials, 4-249, 1835 (Box 540)
- November, Civil Trials, 251-404, 1835 (Box 541)
- November, Civil Trials, 406-536, 1835 (Box 542)
- November, Civil Trials, 541-655, 1835 (Box 543)
- November, Criminal Appearances, 1835 (Box 544)
- November, Appeals, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Tidings, 1835 (Box 545)
- November, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-65, 1835 (Box 546)
- November, Judicials, 68-173, 1835 (Box 547)
- November, Judicials, 175-271, 1835 (Box 548)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1-174, 1836 (Box 549)
- March, Civil Appearances, 175-421, 1836 (Box 550)
- March, Civil Trials, 1-152, 1836 (Box 551)
- March, Civil Trials, 154-251, 1836 (Box 552)
- March, Civil Trials, 263-390, 1836 (Box 553)
- March, Civil Trials, 393-510, 1836 (Box 554)
- March, Criminal Appearances, 2-195, 1836 (Box 555)
- March, Criminal Appearances, 197-221, Criminal Trials, Appeals, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1836 (Box 556)
- March, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-20, 1836 (Box 557)
- March, Judicials, 22-225, Recognizances, 1836 (Box 558)
- November, Civil Appearances, 1-146, 1836 (Box 559)
- November, Civil Appearances, 185-371, 1836 (Box 560)
- November, Civil Appearances, 384-645, 1836 (Box 561)
- November, Civil Trials, 11-313, 1836 (Box 562)
- November, Civil Trials, 315-431, Appeals, 1836 (Box 563)
- November, Criminal Appearances, 1-122, 1836 (Box 564)
- November, Criminal Appearances, 124-183, Criminal Trials, Recognizances, 1836 (Box 565)
- November, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-73, 1836 (Box 566)
- November, Judicials, 75-215, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1836 (Box 567)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1-182, 1837 (Box 568)
- March, Civil Appearances, 184-448, 1837 (Box 569)
- March, Civil Trials, 4-152, 1837 (Box 570)
- March, Civil Trials, 156-247, 1837 (Box 571)
- March, Civil Trials, 249-372, 1837 (Box 572)
- March, Civil Trials, 374-422, 1837 (Box 573)
- March, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1837 (Box 574)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, 1837 (Box 575)
- March, Judicials, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1837 (Box 576)
- November, Civil Appearances, 2-160, 1837 (Box 577)
- November, Civil Appearances, 161-351, 1837 (Box 578)
- November, Civil Appearances, 354-653, Civil Trials, 2-117, 1837 (Box 579)
- November, Civil Trials, 119-364, 1837 (Box 580)
- November, Civil Trials, 366-434, Recognizances, Criminal Trials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1837 (Box 581)
- November, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, 1837 (Box 582)
- November, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-90, 1837 (Box 583)
- November, Judicials, 91-375, 1837 (Box 584)
- March, Civil Appearances, 2-183, 1838 (Box 585)
- March, Civil Appearances, 186-470, 1838 (Box 586)
- March, Civil Trials, 19-179, 1838 (Box 587)
- March, Civil Trials, 182-311, 1838 (Box 588)
- March, Civil Trials, 313-131, 1838 (Box 589)
- March, Appeals, Criminal Appearances & Trials, 1838 (Box 590)
- March, Imparlances, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1838 (Box 591)
- March, Judicials, 1838 (Box 592)
- November, Civil Appearances, 1-181, 1838 (Box 593)
- November, Civil Appearances, 183-330, 1838 (Box 594)
- November, Civil Appearances, 332-584, 1838 (Box 595)
- November, Civil Appearances, 588-707, Civil Trials, 1-69, 1838 (Box 596)
- November, Civil Trials, 72-211, 1838 (Box 597)
- November, Civil Trials, 217-348, 1838 (Box 598)
- November, Civil Trials, 350-471, 1838 (Box 599)
- November, Judicials, 1838 (Box 600)
- November, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1838 (Box 601)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1-146, 1839 (Box 602)
- March, Civil Appearances, 148-382, 1839 (Box 603)
- March, Civil Trials, 1-143, 1839 (Box 604)
- March, Civil Trials, 147-275, 1839 (Box 605)
- March, Civil Trials, 277-393, 1839 (Box 606)
- March, Judicials, 1839 (Box 607)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1839 (Box 608)
- November, Civil Appearances, 5-195, 1839 (Box 609)
- November, Civil Appearances, 197-305, 1839 (Box 610)
- November, Civil Appearances, 308-632, 1839 (Box 611)
- November, Civil Trials, 12-188, 1839 (Box 612)
- November, Civil Trials, 190-322, 1839 (Box 613)
- November, Civil Trials, 324-449, 1839 (Box 614)
- November, Judicials, 1839 (Box 615)
- November, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1839 (Box 616)
- March, Civil Appearances, 10-148, 1840 (Box 617)
- March, Civil Appearances, 150-428, 1840 (Box 618)
- March, Civil Trials, 26-210, 1840 (Box 619)
- March, Civil Trials, 214-314, 1840 (Box 620)
- March, Judicials, 1840 (Box 621)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1840 (Box 622)
- November, Civil Appearances, 1-224, 1840 (Box 623)
- November, Civil Appearances, 227-666, 1840 (Box 624)
- November, Civil Trials, 11-154, 1840 (Box 625)
- November, Civil Trials, 157-252, 1840 (Box 626)
- November, Civil Trials, 255-373, 1840 (Box 627)
- November, Civil Trials, 376-453, 1840 (Box 628)
- November, Judicials, 1840 (Box 629)
- November, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1840 (Box 630)
- March, Civil Appearances, 6-177, 1841 (Box 631)
- March, Civil Appearances, 179-460, 1841 (Box 632)
- March, Civil Trials, 2-124, 1841 (Box 633)
- March, Civil Trials, 128-248, 1841 (Box 634)
- March, Civil Trials, 256-349, 1841 (Box 635)
- March, Judicials, 1841 (Box 636)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1841 (Box 637)
- November, Civil Appearances, 1-210, 1841 (Box 638)
- November, Civil Appearances, 212-334, 1841 (Box 639)
- November, Civil Appearances, 336-674, 1841 (Box 640)
- November, Civil Trials, 6-161, 1841 (Box 641)
- November, Civil Trials, 168-327, 1841 (Box 642)
- November, Civil Trials, 329-437, 1841 (Box 643)
- November, Judicials, 1-121, 1841 (Box 644)
- November, Judicials, 123-173, Appeals, Imparlances, Titlings, 1841 (Box 645)
- March, Civil Appearances, 2-174, 1842 (Box 646)
- March, Civil Appearances, 176-486, 1842 (Box 647)
- March, Civil Trials, 26-145, 1842 (Box 648)
- March, Civil Trials, 148-301, 1842 (Box 649)
- March, Civil Trials, 304-413, 1842 (Box 650)
- March, Judicials, 1842 (Box 651)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1842 (Box 652)
- November, Civil Appearances, 1-163, 1842 (Box 653)
- November, Civil Appearances, 166-430, 1842 (Box 654)
- November, Civil Appearances, 451-797, 1842 (Box 655)
- November, Civil Trials, 6-214, 1842 (Box 656)
- November, Civil Trials, 217-330, 1842 (Box 657)
- November, Civil Trials, 332-473, 1842 (Box 658)
- November, Judicials, 1842 (Box 659)
- November, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1842 (Box 660)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1-149, 1843 (Box 661)
- March, Civil Appearances, 151-477, 1843 (Box 662)
- March, Civil Trials, 14-147, 1843 (Box 663)
- March, Civil Trials, 150-248, 1843 (Box 664)
- March, Civil Trials, 249-366, 1843 (Box 665)
- March, Civil Trials, 368-458, 1843 (Box 666)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1843 (Box 667)
- March, Judicials, 1843 (Box 668)
- November, Civil Appearances, 2-244, 1843 (Box 669)
- November, Civil Appearances, 256-505, Civil Trials, 16-143, 1843 (Box 670)
- November, Civil Trials, 148-256, 1843 (Box 671)
- November, Civil Trials, 258-373, 1843 (Box 672)
- November, Civil Trials, 377-488, 1843 (Box 673)
- November, Civil Trials, 491-543, Appeals, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1843 (Box 674)
- November, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-95, 1843 (Box 675)
- November, Judicials, 98-198, 1843 (Box 676)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1-229, 1844 (Box 677)
- March, Civil Appearances, 239-300, Civil Trials, 4-113, 1844 (Box 678)
- March, Civil Trials, 113-259, 1844 (Box 679)
- March, Civil Trials, 260-388, 1844 (Box 680)
- March, Civil Trials, 390-417, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, Judicials, 1-18, 1844 (Box 681)
- March, Judicials, 20-225, 1844 (Box 682)
- November, Civil Appearances, 4-221, 1844 (Box 683)
- November, Civil Appearances, 236-352, Civil Trials, 16-269, 1844 (Box 684)
- November, Civil Trials, 271-372, Appeals, Imparlances, 1844 (Box 685)
- November, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1844 (Box 686)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1845 (Box 687)
- March, Civil Trials, 1-227, 1845 (Box 688)
- March, Civil Trials, 231-424, 1845 (Box 689)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1845 (Box 690)
- October, Civil Appearances, 6-182, 1845 (Box 691)
- October, Civil Appearances, 184-410, Civil Trials, 13-89, 1845 (Box 692)
- October, Civil Trials, 93-304, 1845 (Box 693)
- October, Civil Trials, 306-383, Appeals, Imparlances, 1845 (Box 694)
- October, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1845 (Box 695)
- March, Civil Appearances, 2-371, 1846 (Box 696)
- March, Civil Trials, 7-258, 1846 (Box 697)
- March, Civil Trials, 261-324, Imparlances, 1846 (Box 698)
- March, Appeals, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1846 (Box 699)
- October, Civil Appearances, 1-186, 1846 (Box 700)
- October, Civil Appearances, 193-656, Civil Trials, 9-137, 1846 (Box 701)
- October, Civil Trials, 139-321, 1846 (Box 702)
- October, Civil Trials, 325-399, Imparlances, 1846 (Box 703)
- October, Appeals, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1846 (Box 704)
- March, Civil Appearances, 4-343, 1847 (Box 705)
- March, Civil Appearances, 355-445, Civil Trials, 2-223, 1847 (Box 706)
- March, Civil Trials, 225-390, 1847 (Box 707)
- March, Civil Trials, 392-411, Appeals, Imparlances, 1847 (Box 708)
- March, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1847 (Box 709)
- October, Civil Appearances, 8-246, 1847 (Box 710)
- October, Civil Appearances, 249-420, Civil Trials, 3-164, 1847 (Box 711)
- October, Civil Trials, 167-331, 1847 (Box 712)
- October, Civil Trials, 337-460, 1847 (Box 713)
- October, Civil Trials, 461-566, Appeals, Rough Bundle, 1847 (Box 714)
- October, Imparlances, 1847 (Box 715)
- October, Judicials, 1847 (Box 716)
- March, Civil Appearances, 7-199, 1848 (Box 717)
- March, Civil Appearances, 203-362, Civil Trials, 17-126, 1848 (Box 718)
- March, Civil Trials, 132-320, 1848 (Box 719)
- March, Civil Trials, 321-463, 1848 (Box 720)
- March, Civil Trials, 466-498, Appeals, Imparlances, 1848 (Box 721)
- March, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1848 (Box 722)
- October, Civil Appearances, 1-321, 1848 (Box 723)
- October, Civil Appearances, 327-466, Civil Trials, 11-215, 1848 (Box 724)
- October, Civil Trials, 222-366, 1848 (Box 725)
- October, Civil Trials, 366-434, Imparlances, 1848 (Box 726)
- October, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1848 (Box 727)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1-281, 1849 (Box 728)
- March, Civil Appearances, 285-431, Civil Trials, 21-255, 1849 (Box 729)
- March, Civil Trials, 257-415, 1849 (Box 730)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1849 (Box 731)
- March, Judicials, 1849 (Box 732)
- October, Civil Appearances, 1-253, 1849 (Box 733)
- October, Civil Appearances, 254-422, Civil Trials, 6-159, 1849 (Box 734)
- October, Civil Trials, 163-327, 1849 (Box 735)
- October, Civil Trials, Appeals, Imparlances, 329-404, 1849 (Box 736)
- October, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1849 (Box 737)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1-215, 1850 (Box 738)
- March, Civil Appearances, 221-404, Civil Trials, 15-192, 1850 (Box 739)
- March, Civil Trials, 193-363, 1850 (Box 740)
- March, Civil Trials, 367-429, Appeals, Imparlances, 1850 (Box 741)
- March, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1850 (Box 742)
- October, Civil Appearances, 1-180, 1850 (Box 743)
- October, Civil Appearances, 181-435, Appeals, 1850 (Box 744)
- October, Civil Trials, 3-260, 1850 (Box 745)
- October, Civil Trials, 262-376, Rough Bundle, 1850 (Box 746)
- October, Imparlances, Titlings, 1850 (Box 747)
- October, Judicials, 1850 (Box 748)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1851 (Box 749)
- March, Civil Trials, 15-271, 1851 (Box 750)
- March, Civil Trials, 275-380, Judicials, 1851 (Box 751)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1851 (Box 752)
- October, Civil Appearances, 3-221, 1851 (Box 753)
- October, Civil Appearances, 222-378, Civil Trials, 5-243, 1851 (Box 754)
- October, Civil Trials, 245-377, 1851 (Box 755)
- October, Appeals, Judicials, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1851 (Box 756)
- March, Civil Appearances, 2-272, 1852 (Box 757)
- March, Civil Appearances, 280-378, Civil Trials, 4-223, 1852 (Box 758)
- March, Civil Trials, 225-333, Appeals, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1852 (Box 759)
- March, Imparlances, Judicials, 1852 (Box 760)
- October, Civil Appearances, 11-212, 1852 (Box 761)
- October, Civil Appearances, 215-533, 1852 (Box 762)
- October, Civil Trials, 6-238, 1852 (Box 763)
- October, Civil Trials, 241-390, Appeals, 1852 (Box 764)
- October, Imparlances, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1852 (Box 765)
- March, Civil Appearances, 8-184, 1853 (Box 766)
- March, Civil Appearances, 188-499, Civil Trials, 9-158, 1853 (Box 767)
- March, Civil Trials, 162-372, 1853 (Box 768)
- March, Civil Trials, 375-431, Imparlances, 1853 (Box 769)
- March, Judicials, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1853 (Box 770)
- October, Civil Appearances, 1-203, 1853 (Box 771)
- October, Civil Appearances, 207-532, Civil Trials, 31-220, 1853 (Box 772)
- October, Civil Trials, 222-403, 1853 (Box 773)
- October, Civil Trials, 406-450, Appeals, Judicials, 1853 (Box 774)
- October, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1853 (Box 775)
- March, Civil Appearances, 12-212, 1854 (Box 776)
- March, Civil Appearances, 213-595, 1854 (Box 777)
- March, Civil Trials, 2-311, 1854 (Box 778)
- March, Civil Trials, 314-452, 1854 (Box 779)
- March, Appeals, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1854 (Box 780)
- March, Judicials, 1854 (Box 781)
- October, Civil Appearances, 3-221, 1854 (Box 782)
- October, Civil Appearances, 224-723, 1854 (Box 783)
- October, Civil Trials, 6-265, 1854 (Box 784)
- October, Civil Trials, 268-437, 1854 (Box 785)
- October, Civil Trials, 439-539, Appeals, 1854 (Box 786)
- October, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1854 (Box 787)
- October, Judicials, 1854 (Box 788)
- March, Civil Appearances, 6-294, 1855 (Box 789)
- March, Civil Appearances, 304-1000, 1855 (Box 790)
- March, Civil Trials, 11-313, 1855 (Box 791)
- March, Civil Trials, 315-460, 1855 (Box 792)
- March, Civil Trials, 463-531, Appeals, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1855 (Box 793)
- March, Imparlances, 1855 (Box 794)
- March, Judicials, 1855 (Box 795)
- October, Civil Appearances, 1-230, 1855 (Box 796)
- October, Civil Appearances, 233-726, 1855 (Box 797)
- October, Civil Appearances, 737-1058, Civil Trials, 16-233, 1855 (Box 798)
- October, Civil Trials, 240-420, 1855 (Box 799)
- October, Civil Trials, 422-589, 1855 (Box 800)
- October, Civil Trials, 591-626, Appeals, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1855 (Box 801)
- October, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-22, 1855 (Box 802)
- October, Judicials, 26-195, 1855 (Box 803)
- March, Civil Appearances, 1-168, 1856 (Box 804)
- March, Civil Appearances, 170-714, 1856 (Box 805)
- March, Civil Appearances, 721-890, Civil Trials, 6-211, 1856 (Box 806)
- March, Civil Trials, 213-452, 1856 (Box 807)
- March, Civil Trials, 454-592, 1856 (Box 808)
- March, Civil Trials, 594-764, 1856 (Box 809)
- March, Civil Trials, 766-883, Appeals, 1856 (Box 810)
- March, Imparlances, 1-604, 1856 (Box 811)
- March, Imparlances, 606-1138, Judicials, 1-72, 1856 (Box 812)
- March, Judicials, 74-192, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1856 (Box 813)
- October, Civil Appearances, 1-261, 1856 (Box 814)
- October, Civil Appearances, 262-515, 1856 (Box 815)
- October, Civil Appearances, 523-1048, 1856 (Box 816)
- October, Civil Trials, 16-369, 1856 (Box 817)
- October, Civil Trials, 370-538, 1856 (Box 818)
- October, Civil Trials, 540-688, 1856 (Box 819)
- October, Civil Trials, 691-857, 1856 (Box 820)
- October, Civil Trials, 859-953, Appeals, 1856 (Box 821)
- October, Imparlances, 1856 (Box 822)
- October, Judicials, 2-193, 1856 (Box 823)
- October, Judicials, 197-344, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1856 (Box 824)
- March, Civil Appearances, 2-226, 1857 (Box 825)
- March, Civil Appearances, 227-434, 1857 (Box 826)
- March, Civil Appearances, 437-807, Civil Trials, 18-235, 1857 (Box 827)
- March, Civil Trials, 238-485, 1857 (Box 828)
- March, Civil Trials, 487-642, 1857 (Box 829)
- March, Civil Trials, 649-814, 1857 (Box 830)
- March, Civil Trials, 816-863, Imparlances, 1-454, 1857 (Box 831)
- March, Imparlances, 455-1123, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1857 (Box 832)
- March, Judicials, 1-158, 1857 (Box 833)
- March, Judicials, 160-311, Appeals, 1857 (Box 834)
- October, Civil Appearances, 2-216, 1857 (Box 835)
- October, Civil Appearances, 218-525, 1857 (Box 836)
- October, Civil Appearances, 526-1225, 1857 (Box 837)
- October, Civil Trials, 1-150, 1857 (Box 838)
- October, Civil Trials, 152-446, 1857 (Box 839)
- October, Civil Trials, 448-630, 1857 (Box 840)
- October, Civil Trials, 631-822, 1857 (Box 841)
- October, Civil Trials, 824-1024, 1857 (Box 842)
- October, Civil Trials, 1025-1199, 1857 (Box 843)
- October, Civil Trials, 1201-1411, 1857 (Box 844)
- October, Civil Trials, 1417-1609, 1857 (Box 845)
- October, Civil Trials, 1611-1760, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, 1857 (Box 846)
- October, Appeals, Judicials, 1-149, 1857 (Box 847)
- October, Judicials, 151-328, 1857 (Box 848)
- October, Judicials, 330-460, Titlings for Writs, 1857 (Box 849)
- January, Civil Appearances, 3-174, 1858 (Box 850)
- January, Civil Appearances, 176-532, 1858 (Box 851)
- January, Civil Appearances, 553-763, Civil Trials, 1858 (Box 852)